<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<journey name="Main calculator screen Journey">
    <description>Test main ratio calculator screen</description>
    <actions xml:space="preserve">
        <action>Action 1: Clear Input Fields
- Click 'Clear fields' button.
- All input fields are empty.</action>
        <action>Action 2: Validate First Ratio Preset
- Tap the first ratio button.
- Confirm the Width and Height fields of the original size section, are automatically populated with the ratio values shown on the ratio button we clicked.
- Tap the Calculate button.
- Confirm a visual shape is displayed that matches the selected ratio.
- Verify that the calculated aspect ratio value is displayed as a number.</action>
        <action>Action 3: Custom Calculation with Second Ratio Preset
- Tap the second ratio button.
- Confirm the Width and Height fields of the original size section, are automatically populated with the ratio values shown on the ratio button we clicked.
- Enter 100 into the Width field under New Size
- Tap the Calculate button
- Confirm a visual shape is displayed that matches the selected ratio.
- Verify the result section shows two rows of numbers:
	1.	The calculated resolution (matching the input width and the corresponding calculated height).
	2.	The numerical result of the aspect ratio division (e.g., 4 : 3 = 1.33).</action>
        <action>Action 4: Custom Calculation with Height selection
- Enter 100 into the Height field under New Size
- Confirm Width in New Size section is clear now
- Tap the Calculate button
- Confirm a visual shape is displayed that matches the selected ratio.
- Verify the result section shows two rows of numbers:
	1.	The calculated resolution (matching the input height and the corresponding calculated width).
	2.	The numerical result of the aspect ratio division (e.g., 4 : 3 = 1.33).</action>
        <action>Action 5: Check auto clearance on selection
- Enter 200 into the Width field under New Size
- Confirm Height in New Size section is clear now</action>
        <action>Action 6: Confirm that the ad banner is visible
- Confirm that the ad banner is visible at the bottom of the screen</action>
        <action>Action 7: Open help dialog
- Press the lightbulb icon at the toolbar
- Confirm you are seeing a dialog that explains some things about aspect ratio
- Press the button
- Confirm that you are back to main calculator screen</action>
        </actions>
</journey>
